This cake is amazing!
这蛋糕太好吃了
My God, get a room.
天啊，你躲一边吃吧。
I would get a room with this cake.
躲一边儿干啥？
I think I could show this cake a good time.
正是时候让你们看看美味的蛋糕呢。
If you had to, what would you give up, food or sex?
如果你们必须放弃一样的话 你们会放弃哪一样儿，食物还是性爱？
Sex.
性爱
Seriously, answer faster.
说真的，你回答得也太快了吧
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
不好意思，亲爱的
But when she said "sex", I wasn't thinking about sex with you.
我刚才说的性爱，并不是指和你一起的性爱
It's like a giant hug.
好象我还受了很大恩惠似的。
Ross, how about you? Which would you give up?
罗斯，你呢？ 你会放弃哪一样？性爱还是食物？
Food.
食物
How about sex or dinosaurs?
那如果是性爱和恐龙呢？
Oh, my God, it's like Sophie's Choice.
老天啊，就像是“索菲的选择”
Oh, God.
哦，天啊
What about you, Joe? What would you give up, sex or food?
乔伊，你放弃什么？性爱还是食物？
I don't know, it's too hard.
我不知道，这太难取舍了
No, you gotta pick one.
不行，你必须得选一个
Food. No, sex.
食物，不，性爱
Food. Sex. Food. Sex.. I don't know! Oh, God, I want both!
食物，性爱，食物，性爱… 我不知道，老天，我都想要！
I want.. I want girls on bread!
我要坐在面包上的妞儿！
The One Where Chandler Gets Caught
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
-You gotta see these pictures of Emma. -Oh, how cute!
-我这儿有我女儿最新的照片 -哇，真可爱啊
-She looks just like a little doll. -Oh, no, that is a doll.
-她看上去就象个洋娃娃 -不不，那就是个洋娃娃
Oh, thank God, because that thing's really creepy.
噢，感谢上帝，因为我觉得它看上去有点吓人
Look, there's Chandler.
钱德在那儿
Who's the blond? She's pretty.
噢，那个金发女郎是谁？她很漂亮
He's having an affair.
他有外遇了
He is not having an affair!
他才不是有外遇呢
I'm always right about these things.
你知道的啦，我在这事儿上面感觉很准的。
No, you're not. Last week, you thought Ross was trying to kill you.
不，你才没有呢 上周你还在想罗斯想把你宰了
Well, sorry, but it's hard to believe that anyone would tell a story that dull..
对不起，但确实很让人难以相信 有人能讲一个洋娃娃...
just to tell it.
也会讲的故事。
There's something going on with them.
我敢发誓他们俩之间肯定有些什么事
Look! He's getting into the car with her.
快看，他们俩上了同一部车
That doesn't mean anything.
那并不能说明什么
Oh, yeah? Well, let's see.
是吗？让我们走着瞧
Okay, duck down.
喂, 趴低点
-Hello? -Hi, Chandler. It's Phoebe.
-喂? -嗨，钱德，我是菲比
I know that Monica is working today..
我知道今天莫尼卡要上班
so I was wondering if you wanted to come to the movies with me and Rachel.
所以我想你要不要跟我和瑞秋一起去看电影
Oh, I have to work too. Yeah, I'm stuck here at the office all day.
噢，我也得上班。 我在这办公室里都闷了有一天了
Well, it's a shame that you'll miss the movie..
太可惜了，你不能去看电影
because we were gonna see, you know, either Liar Liar..
因为我们打算看《骗子，骗子》
or Betrayal or An Affair to Remember.
《背叛》或者是《不了情》
Those are all really old.
噢，这些片子很新啊
Okay, then maybe it'll be..
是啊，也可能会看。。。
Dude, Where's My Car?
老兄，我的车呢?
-What? -They're in a car.
-什么？ -他们现在在车里
Okay. Well, talk to you later, okay? Bye.
好了，迟点再跟你说，再见
Jeez!
Okay, quick. We gotta find a cab and follow them.
快，我们得拦辆的士跟踪他们
Yeah, okay. Let me just grab my night-vision goggles and my stun gun.
好的，我得先去拿我的夜视镜和眩晕枪
I got them.
我这儿有
-Hey. -Hey. Hi, sweetie.
-嘿 -嗨，亲爱的
Hey, you smell like perfume and cigarettes.
你身上有香水和香烟的味道
-I was in the car with Nancy. -Nancy doesn't smoke.
-我今天和南茜在车里面呆了一天 -南茜可不抽烟
Well, at least the perfume's not mine. Be thankful for that.
那至少那香水不是我的 你这点倒是不用担心。
So.. What did you think of the house?
那么，你认为那房子怎么样？
It's everything we've been looking for.
简直太棒了，就是我们一直以来要找的
Isn't it? And what about the amazing wanes coating..
是吗？那些漂亮的涂层，冠形屋顶
the crown molding and the dormer windows in the attic?
偏厦窗子和阁楼？
And the wiggle woms and the zip zorps!
还有蠕虫和爬虫？
What were the things you said?
你刚刚在说什么？
-Don't you love the huge yard? -The fireplace in the bedroom.
-你喜欢那个大院子吗？ -还有睡房里的壁炉
And Nancy said it's really underpriced..
南茜还说这个价钱非常优惠
because the guy lost his job and has to move in with his parents!
因为那家伙丢了工作不得不搬去跟父母住 所以急于出手。
This is bringing out a lovely color in you.
看把你兴奋的
So do you think we should get it?
你认为我们是不是应该把它买下来？
I don't know. What do you think?
我不知道，你怎么想？
-I think we should. -I do too.
-我想我们应该买下来 -我也这么想
This is huge. How bad do you wanna smoke right now?
这是很大件事。 现在想不想抽一支？
I don't know what you mean, giant, talking cigarette.
你说什么呢，进言有功奖励香烟？
Phoebe called as I was getting into Nancy's car.
对了，我正在南茜车上的时候，菲比打电话来了
If she asks you, I was at work all day.
如果她问起就说我一天都在工作
Got you. When do we tell them?
明白，你打算什么时候跟他们说这件事
We don't. Not until it's 100 percent. Why upset everybody over nothing?
至少要等到事情完全确定下来，我是说 八字还没一撇，没有必要让大家都难受
Okay. Right.
嗯，好的
-Oh, my God, that is gonna be so hard. -I know. Good luck with it.
-上帝，这将会非常难受 -我知道。一切顺利吧
I just can't see Chandler cheating.
我只是不明白钱德为什么要骗莫尼卡
I'm telling you guys, we followed them out to a house in Westchester.
告诉你们吧，我们一直跟踪他们 到一所位于西切斯特的房子的外面
They went in for 45 minutes, and then they came out looking pretty happy.
他们在里面待了有45分钟， 出来的时候两人看上去都很高兴
Chandler?
钱德？
Forty-five minutes?
45分钟？
Well, something's not right.
肯定有什么地方不对头
So you went all the way to Westchester, waited 45 minutes..
所以你们跟踪到 西切斯特  还在外面等了45分钟
-and came back in a cab? -Yeah.
-然后坐出租车回来？ -是啊
If each of you guys would like to pitch in 100 bucks, that would be great.
如果你们谁愿意扔个100大元进去 那真是太好了
I can't believe he'd do this to Monica.
我不敢相信他这样对莫尼卡
I know, and with the baby coming?
是啊，而且他们就快有小孩了
-So should we tell her? -I don't know.
-那我们该不该告诉莫尼卡？ -我不知道
If one of us saw Mike with another woman, would you want us to tell you?
菲比，如果我们看到麦克跟另一个女人在一起， 我们应不应该告诉你？
Why? Who'd you see him with?
什么？你看到他跟谁在一起了？
-No one. I'm just saying if we did.. -Tell me what you know!
-没有，我只是说 -告诉我你知道些什么！
No one! Nothing! Mike's a great guy! It was hypothetical!
我什么也不知道，我只是假设
All right. He is a good guy.
好了，好了，他是个好人
You're right. He wouldn't cheat.
是啊，他是个好人，他不会骗我的
If I did see him with someone, there's no way I..
如果我真看到他跟另一个女人在一起。。。
Who did you see him with?
你看见他跟谁在一起了？
Oh, look at her. So happy.
看，她多开心啊
If only there were a smaller one to clean this one.
要是有更小的来清理这个该有多好
Hey, is Chandler here?
钱德在吗？
No, he's picking up dinner. Why? What's up?
不在，他去买晚餐去了，出什么事了吗？
Look, whatever happens, we're here for you, and we love you.
无论发生什么事， 我们都跟你在一起，我们爱你
-All right. -We think Chandler might be having an affair.
-好 -我想钱德可能有外遇了
-What? -Phoebe and I saw Chandler..
-什么？ -菲比和我今天
with a blond woman today outside on the street.
看见钱德和一个金发女郎在一起
And then we followed them to a house in Westchester.
然后我们跟踪他们到了 一所位于西切斯特的房子
They went in together. I'm so sorry.
他们一起进去了，很抱歉
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, that's awful.
我的上帝。。。 太可怕了。
What did you think of the house?
你觉得房子怎么样?
What?
什么？
Monica, you understand what we're saying, right?
莫尼卡 你明白我刚才说的话 对不对？
Yeah. Sure. I mean, I'm devastated, obviously.
明白，当然明白 非常清楚你的意思
Did you think the neighborhood was homey?
你们认为那些邻居热不热情？
-Hey. -You son of a bitch.
-嘿！ -你这个狗杂种
Is it me, or have the greetings gone downhill around here?
你是在说我还是说 那个在这附近游荡的进过局子的毒贩？
Phoebe and Rachel saw you with Nancy today.
菲比和瑞秋今天看见你和南茜在一起
They think you're having an affair.
他们以为你和她有一腿
-Who's Nancy? -What's going on?
-谁是南茜？ -到底是怎么回事？
Okay..
好的。。。
All right, you better sit down.
好的，好的，伙计们，坐下说话
-This is.. This is pretty big. -Yeah.
-这是件大事 -是的
I'm not having an affair.
我没有外遇
Nancy is our realtor.
南茜是我们的房地产经纪
I knew he couldn't be with a woman for 45 minutes!
我就知道他不可能跟一个女人做45分钟那么长
Why do you have a realtor?
你们为什么要请地产经纪？
She's been showing us houses outside of the city.
最近以来她带着我们去看市区以外的房子
-What? -Are you serious?
-什么？ -你是说真的？
When we found out that we were gonna get this baby..
我们认为因为我们马上就要有小孩了
Chandler and I decided we didn't want to raise a kid in the city.
我和钱德决定 我们不能在市区抚养我们的小孩
So you're.. So you're gonna move?
所以你们要搬出去？
Oh, my God.
我的上帝！
Shouldn't we all vote on stuff like this?
这种事我们总要投票解决吧？
What is wrong with raising a kid in the city?
在市区里带小孩有什么不妥吗？
I'm doing it. Ross is doing it.
我不就正在市区里带小孩吗？ 罗斯也是
Sarah Jessica Parker is doing it!
莎拉.杰西卡.派克也是这么干的
And that's great for you guys, but we want a lawn and a swing set.
对你们来说这没什么问题 但是我们想要一个长长的秋千
A street where our kids can ride their bikes..
还有一条小孩可以在上面骑单车的马路
and maybe an ice-cream truck can go by.
不时还会有雪糕车经过
So you want to buy a house in the '50s.
所以你们想买一栋50年代的房子？
Have you thought about what you're giving up?
你们有没有想过你们正放弃什么么？
You can't move out of the city. What if..?
你们不能搬出市区
What if you want Chinese food at 5 a.m.?
要是，要是你们想凌晨五点钟吃中餐怎么办？
Or a fake Rolex that breaks as soon as it rains?
又或者想买一块一响就散架的假劳力士怎么办？
Or an Asian hooker sent right to your door?
又或者是想电召一个亚洲妓女怎么办？
You know what? If you want to look for a house, that's okay.
知道吗？ 如果你们只是想看看房子，没问题
No! No, it's not! Don't listen to him. I'm gonna thump you.
不，不， 不，别听他的 小心我扁你
It's okay, because they have to get it out of their system.
的确是没问题，但等你们真正住进去之后
Okay? But you're gonna realize this is the only place you want to be.
你们会发现这里才是你们真正想要住的地方
Actually..
实际上
we already found a house we love.
我们已经找到合我们心意的房子了
-What? -About an hour ago, we made an offer.
-什么？ -大约一小时以前，我们开出了我们的价码
Bet you wish I was having an affair now, huh?
我打赌你们现在宁可我有外遇
-You put an offer on a house? -It's so sweet.
-你们已经开出价码了？ -那房子真的很好
It really is. It has this big yard that leads down to this stream.
的确是，那里有一个很大的院子 一直通到一条小溪
And then there's these old maple trees.
那里还有很多枫树
Oh, again with the nature. What are you, beavers?
跟自然环境有什么关系？ 你们又不是水獭
Look, I know this is really hard, and we're really sorry.
我知道你们一时很难接受我们的决定， 我们也非常的抱歉
Is this because I come over here without knocking and eat your food?
是不是因为我常常不敲门 就过来拿你们的东西吃?
Because I can stop doing that.
我可以不那样做
I really, really think I can.
我真的可以改
You know that's not the reason, Joe.
乔伊, 你知道这不是我们要搬出去住的原因
I think if you saw it, you'd understand.
我想如果你们到实地看一看的话 你们会明白的
You guys were there. It's beautiful, isn't it?
你们俩去看过，那的确很美，不是吗？
-Yeah, it is. -What the hell are you doing?
-是，确实是很美 -你在干什么？
Well, it is, all right? When we were out there today, all I kept thinking was:
我的意思是我们今天到那儿的时候 我所想的是
"I can't believe Chandler's screwing this woman..
我简直不敢相信钱德在和那女人干那事儿，
but, man, this would be a nice place to live!"
但那并不意味那里不是一个适合居住的地方！
Yeah, but so is this.
是，但漂亮又能怎样？
Yeah. I mean, if you move there, you have to leave here.
对，我是说如果你们搬到那里去住 你们就得离开这儿了
I mean, how can you leave this place?
你们怎么能离开这个地方？
Come on, Daddy, listen!
爸，你听我说
All my life, everyone's always told me, "You're a shoe!"
这就好象是我生命的全部 每个人总是对我说 "你是鞋子！"
"You're a shoe! You're a shoe. You're a shoe!"
你是鞋子！你是鞋子，你是鞋子！
I stopped and said, "What if I don't want to be a shoe?
今天我停下来说 如果我不想当鞋子会怎样？
What if I want to be a purse?
如果我想做手袋？
Or a hat?"
或是帽子？
I don't want you to buy me a hat, I..
不，我不是要你给我买顶帽子
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
我是说我是…啊…我只是打个比方，爸！
You can see where he'd have trouble.
你知道他的麻烦在哪里了
Well, maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
好吧，也许我应该和莫尼卡待在这儿
I guess we've established she's staying with Monica.
我猜她的意思是，我们已经就 谁和莫尼卡住在一起这个问题达成了共识
Your money's mine, Greene.
你的钱要归我啦，格林小姐。
Your fly's open, Geller.
你的尿门没拉上，盖勒先生。
You know what I just realized?
伙计们，知道我刚发现了什么吗？
"Joker" is "poker" with a "J"!
Joker是带"J"的Poker
Coincidence?
巧合吧？
That's "joincidence" with a "C"!
嗯，那是带"C"的'joincidence'
Look! Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
呃，看，那个奇丑的裸男点了一堆蜡烛
That had to hurt!
那太痛苦了
Hey, it's your Thanksgiving too.
嗨，这也是你们的感恩节
Instead of watching football, you could help.
除了看球赛，你也可以过来帮我们干点活
We know.
我们会的
Rachel, you want to put the marshmallows in concentric circles.
好了，瑞秋， 你想把这些软糖粒摆成一个同心圆
No, Mon. You want to put them in concentric circles.
不，莫尼卡， 是你想把它们摆成那样
I want to do this.
我只是想这样
Every year.
每年如是
It's stuck!
我被卡住了！
Step.
别着急，小心阶梯
How did it get on?
你怎么会把头给套进去了？
I put it on to scare Chandler.
我想把它戴上去吓吓钱德
Oh, my God! Monica's going to totally freak out!
我的上帝，莫尼卡会被吓死的
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
还有，这里面难闻得要命
Of course it smells bad. You have your head up a turkey's ass.
那是当然了 你脑袋伸到火鸡的屁股里面去了
Monica.
莫尼卡
Did you get the turkey..?
嗨，你们把火鸡涂上油没有？
Oh, my God!
啊，我的上帝，我的上帝
Who is that?
这是谁？
It's Joey.
是乔伊
I got it!
我明白了。
If we win, they have to get rid of the rooster.
如果我们赢，你们就得把那公鸡拿走
That's interesting!
这主意怎么样？
If you win..
如果你们赢。。
we give up the bird.
我们就放弃那只鸟儿
But if we win..
但是，如果我们赢了
we get your apartment.
我们要你们住的地方
-Deal! -What?
-一言为定！ -什么？
"Monica's nickname when she was a hockey goalie?"
莫妮卡当曲棍球守门员时候的绰号
-Big Fat Goalie. -Correct!
-大胖守门员 -正确。
"Rachel claims it's her favorite movie."
瑞秋说她最喜欢的电影是？
Dangerous Liaisons.
孽恋焚情
-"Her actual favorite movie is..?" -Weekend at Bernie's.
-正确。实际上她最喜欢的电影是？ -老板渡假去
"Monica categorizes her towels. How many categories are there?"
莫妮卡给她的毛巾分类， 一共分了多少类？
-Everyday use. -Fancy.
-每天用的 -正确
-Guest. -Fancy guest.
-客人的 -正确
-Two seconds. -Eleven?
-2秒 -11种？
Unbelievable! Eleven is correct.
太另人难以置信了，11是正确答案
"Chandler was how old when he first touched a girl's breast?"
钱德第一次摸女孩子胸部的时候有多大？
-14? -No,19.
-14? -不, 19.
Thanks, man.
谢了兄弟
"Joey had an imaginary childhood friend.
乔伊有一个想象中的童年时的朋友
-His name was..?" -Maurice!
-他叫什么名字？ -莫里斯
-"His profession was..?" -Space cowboy!
-正确，他是干什么的？ -太空牛仔！
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
钱德是干什么工作的？
Ten seconds. You need this or you lose.
还有10秒，你们得答对这一题，否则就输了
Something to do with transponding.
嗯，好象是跟传送有关的
He's a transponster!
啊，啊，是搬运工！
That's not even a word!
你说的都不是一个正确的单词！
You are mean boys who are just being mean!
你们是些卑鄙的家伙，太卑鄙了!
Don't get mad! No one forced you to raise the stakes.
嗨，别冲我们发火！没人逼你越赌越大
That is not true! She forced me!
不对，是她逼我的！
You got the question wrong.
是你答错题了。
It was a stupid, unfair question!
那是一个愚蠢的，不公平的问题。
Don't blame the questions!
愿赌服输，不要把责任怪在问题上
Stop yelling in our apartment! You are ruining moving day for us.
你们能不能不要在屋子里瞎嚷嚷 你们把我们的搬家日给毁了
Chandler!
钱德！
I saw what you were doing in the window!
钱德，我从窗户那里瞧见你们在干那事儿了
I saw what you're doing to my sister! Get out here!
我看见你在对我妹子做什么！ 现在你给我滚出去！
Listen, we had a good run.
哇！听着，我们很恩爱
What was it? Four, five months?
什么？ 四个月？五个月？
That's more than most people have in a lifetime. Goodbye.
我的意思是 这已经超过大多数人一辈子的恩爱时光了
Hey, Ross. What's up, bro?
嘿，罗斯，出什么事了，老哥？
What the hell are you doing?
你们到底在干什么？！
What's going on?
嘿！出什么事了？
I think Ross knows about me and Monica.
我想，我想罗斯知道我和莫尼卡的事了
Dude, he's right there.
老兄, 他在那呢
I thought you were my best friend! This is my sister!
我还当你是我最好的朋友呢！她可是我妹妹！
My best friend and my sister! I cannot believe this!
我最好的朋友跟我妹妹！我简直不敢相信！
We're not just messing around. I love her.
我们不是玩玩而已的。 我爱她
I'm in love with her.
我跟她坠入情网了
I'm so sorry that you had to find out this way.
真不好意思，你是以这种方式知道我们相恋的
I'm sorry, but it's true. I love him too.
抱歉，但这是真的，我也爱他
My best friend and my sister!
我最好的朋友和我妹妹！
I cannot believe this!
我简直不敢相信！
This is the last box of your clothes.
这是你最后一箱衣服
I'm just gonna label it "What were you thinking?"
我想在这上面贴个标签，上书：你在想什么？
I was gonna go across the hall and write that on Chandler.
有趣，因为我正想到对门去 在钱德身上也写上这句话
Guys, I don't wanna make things worse, but..
二位，我不想把事情搞砸
I don't want to live with Rachel anymore.
但是，嗯，我再也不想跟瑞秋住在一起了
You're so mean to each other.
你们对对方太刻薄了！
I don't wanna end up like that with Rachel. I still like you.
而且我也不想跟瑞秋最后闹得不欢而散 我还是喜欢你
That's fine because I'm not moving.
菲比，那没关系，因为我不搬了
Phoebe, you gotta take her.
哇，哇，哇，菲比，你得跟她一起住！
I said some bad stuff..
你知道，我是曾说过一些她的坏话
but Rachel has qualities that make her a good roommate.
但是，瑞秋还是有很多优点的， 这足以让她成为一个好的室友
She gets tons of catalogs and folds down the pages of things I'd like.
她有很多商品目录，嗯 她会把那些 她认为我会喜欢的产品所在页折起来
What else?
还有呢？
When I take a shower..
我在冲凉的时候...
she leaves me notes on the mirror.
她会在镜子上给我留下留言
I do. I do do that.
是，那是我干的
That's nice. I like having things to read in the bathroom.
很好，我喜欢在洗手间里读点东西
When I fall asleep on the couch..
当我看完书在沙发上睡着的时候，
she covers me with a blanket.
她会为我盖上一条毯子
Well, you know, I don't want you to be cold.
你知道啦，我不想让你着凉了
And when I told her that I was gonna move in with Chandler..
还有，当我告诉她 我要搬过去跟钱德一起住的时候，
she was really supportive.
她真的是很支持我
You were so great.
你太好了
You made it so easy.
你把一件困难的事情变得轻松简单
And now you have to leave.
现在，你得走了
And I have to live with a boy!
而我得和一个男生住在一起！
-She really left. -I know.
-她真的走了 -我知道
-Thank you. -No problem, roomie.
-谢谢 -没问题，室友
-Can I ask you a question? -Sure.
-我能问你一个问题吗？ -当然！
What the hell is that dog doing here?
那只狗倒底在那儿干什么？
A little toast here. Ding, ding!
我来说点祝酒词吧
This isn't exactly the kind of Thanksgiving you planned..
我知道这并不是你们所计划的感恩节
but for me this has been really great.
但对于我来说，这个节真的是太棒了
I think because it didn't involve divorce..
知道吗？我之所以这样认为是因为 这个节里面没有离婚...
or projectile vomiting.
和吐得一塌糊涂
If you had gone to Vail..
无论怎样，我只是在想，如果你们去了Vail
or if you had been with your family, or if you didn't have..
如果你们和你们的家人在一起
syphilis and stuff..
如果你没做性病这类的广告
we wouldn't be all together.
我们就不可能在一起，对不对？
So I guess what I'm trying to say is..
所以，我想我想说的是
that I'm very thankful that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
我很感激你们 因为你们的感恩节计划全砸了
-That's so sweet! -Thank you.
-太感人了 -谢谢
Here's to a lousy Christmas!
为糟糕的圣诞节干杯
And a crappy New Year!
也为糟糕的新年干杯
-Hear, hear! -Hear, hear!
-听着听着！ -听着听着！
You can't move. You just.. You just can't.
你们不能搬，你们就是不能这样做
Rachel's right. This is where you guys belong.
瑞秋说得对，你们俩是属于这里的
You don't wanna live in Westchester. That's the worst of the Chesters.
是啊，你们可不能搬到西切斯特， 听起来就象"死"切斯特。
You know, sometimes when I'm alone in my apartment, I look over here..
知道吗，有时我独自一人在我的寓所的时候 望向这边
and you guys are just having dinner..
你们正在吃晚餐
or watching TV or something..
看电视或是做着其它什么事
but it makes me feel better.
这让我感觉好很多
And now when I look over, who am I gonna see?
现在，你们搬走之后 我再望过来的时候，我会看到谁？
The Gottliebs? The Yangs?
张三？李四？
They don't make me feel so good.
他们不会让我感觉如此之好！
Yeah. So don't move, okay? Just stay here..
是啊，所以别搬了 对，就留下吧
-and maybe close your blinds at night. -Hey.
-晚上的时候别忘了拉窗帘就行了。 -喂！
Hello?
喂?
It's Nancy. They responded to our offer.
是南茜，他们答复我们开出的价码了
And?
然后？
Okay. Thanks.
好的，谢谢
They passed.
他们对我们的出价没兴趣
They said they won't go a penny under the asking price.
他们一个子儿也不愿少
-We can't afford that. -I know.
-我们负担不起那价格 -我知道
Well, there you go.
好了，如你们所愿了
I'm really sorry, you guys.
真抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry too. I'm even more sorry that phone call didn't come..
我也很抱歉。要是那个电话
before I told you about looking through the window.
在我说出从 窗户那边望过来之前打来的话，就好了。
Yeah. Well, we're gonna let you be alone.
我们还是让你们俩单独待一会儿吧
-You gonna be okay? -Yeah, we'll be okay.
-你们没事吧？ -我们没事的
Love you guys.
我爱你们
You know, I'm really sorry I wasn't more supportive before.
很抱歉，刚才没有支持你们
That's okay. We understand.
没关系，我们能理解
Yeah, and about this Nancy..
对了，关于这个南茜
If you're not sleeping with her, should I?
如果你没跟她上床的话，能不能让我上？
I know there'll be other houses, but I just..
我知道外面还有很多房子，但是这栋。。。
-I love that one so much. -Yeah.
-我太爱这栋房子了 -是啊
Well, it's a good thing we got it then.
所以得到这栋房子是天大的喜事
-What? -We got the house.
-什么？ -我们买到那房子了
-Oh, my God. -I didn't wanna tell you in front of them.
-噢，我的上帝 -我只是不想当着他们的面告诉你
We got it?! We got the house?!
我们买到那栋房子了
We're getting a house!
-We're getting a house. -And a baby.
-对，我们买到了 -还有小孩
We're growing up.
我们长大了
We sure are.
是啊。
-Who's gonna tell them? -Not it!
-谁去跟他们说呢？ -不是我
Not it! Damn it!
也不是我
Rachel, this is yours.
瑞秋，这是给你的
Why? What are these for?
为什么送我们这些礼物？
-You'll see. -All right, everybody open them.
-过会你就知道了 -好了，大家都请打开来看看吧
Wow, this is so beautiful!
好漂亮啊
These are the ones I was looking at in the store!
这个正是我上次在商店里相中的那一款小饰品！
-I know. -Oh, I love this!
-我知道 -我喜欢这个
A meatball sub!
喔，一个肉丸包！
Thanks!
谢谢
Seriously, guys, what's going on? What are these for?
说真的，你们怎么了？ 为什么送我们这些礼物？
Well, I didn't know how to tell you before, but...
我先前不知道该怎么跟你们说, 但是...
-We got the house. -Enjoy!
-我们买到那房子了 -各位好好享受吧
What did they say?
他们刚才说什么？